Guide to the Tim Stevens Papers, 1945-2006 AIS.2006.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- NAACP, 1971-2006; 1994-2004; III.
  - Police Affairs, 1990-2004; 14.
    - Hohnsberger, Fred, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Jackson, Jerry, 1995-2001 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Johnson, Shawn, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Jonny Gammage Law Initiative, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Jordan, Damian, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Mayor's Letter, 1990-1995 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Minority Women, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - National March for Justice, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - National Organization for Women, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Notes, 1995-2004 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Omodio, Annette, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Performance Audit, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Police Brutality, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Police Chiefs' Association, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Police Summit, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - "The Police and You", 1996 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Political, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Powell, Lawrence, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Racial Profiling, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Resolution 445, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Rivera, Geraldo, 1998 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Rogers, Bernard, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Stanley, William, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Starks, Anthony, 1995-1997 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Support Committee, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Taylor, Ronald, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Tewolde, Getu, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Traffic Violation, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Tribune-Review, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Use of Force, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Wilbur, John, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Wilson, Troy, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 10-11)
    - Adrienne Young, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Coalition to Counter Hate Groups, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - Public Safety Study, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Political Action, 1992-2005; 15.
    This subseries contains materials relating to political affairs concerning the NAACP, with a main emphasis on voter registration drives, from 1992 to 2005. Included in this are partial records of the Political Action Committee.
    - Act 49 Training, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Activist Debate Network, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - ACORN Vote for Power, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Adams, Harvey, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Allegheny County, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Allegheny County Home Rule, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Allegheny Court of Common Pleas, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Bingler, John, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Black Legislators in Pennsylvania, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - B-PEP, 2000-2004 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Campaign Finance Reform, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Census, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Church Empowerment, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - City Controller's Office, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - City Council, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - City County Conference on Affirmative Action, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - City of Pittsburgh, 1995-2003 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - City Resolutions, 2000-2001 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Cocaine, 1996-1999 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Committee Report, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - County, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - County Council, undated (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - County Executive Candidates, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - County Government, 2000-2002 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - County Home Rule, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Cranmer, Bob, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Dawida-Vuono, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Districts, 1991 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - Election Night Celebration, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - Federal Legislative Workshop, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - General, 1992-2004 (Box 42, Folder 43-48)
    - General, 1992-2004 (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
    - Harrisburg NAACP, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Home Rule, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Jury Pool Forms, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Justice System, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Legislative Report Card, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Manning, Jeffrey, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Matta, George, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Murphy, Tom, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - National Voter Fund, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - National Voter Registration Act, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Onorato, Dan, 2003-2004 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Partisan Politics, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Peduto, William, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania Human Relations Commission, undated (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Petition, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Pittsburgh Financial Oversight Board, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Port Authority, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Portis, Richard, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Prothonotary, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Reapportionment, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Register and Vote, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Relationship with B-PEP, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Rendell, Edward, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Reparations, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Rivers Club, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Roddy, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Robinson, Bill, 1995-2000 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Roll to the Polls, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Santorum, Rick, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Speeches, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Udin, Sala, 2000-2002 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - US Drug Policy, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Voter Education Forum, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Voter Empowerment, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Voter Empowerment Technical Assistance, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Voter Empowerment Training, undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Voter Fund, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Voter Mobilization Coalition, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Voter Registration, 2001-2004 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Voter Registration Guide, undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Voter Roll Call, undated (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Voting Flyers, undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Western Pennsylvania Black Political Assembly, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Candidate Forums, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - GOTV, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 43)
    - House Bill 2576, undated (Box 42, Folder 44)
    - Magistrate Court, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 45)
    - Mike Fisher, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - National Voter Fund, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Press and Publicity, 1974-2006; 16.
    This subseries contains material relating to the press and publicity the NAACP received, mainly in the form of news clippings, articles, and press releases, from 1974 to 2006. Included in this are the partial records of the Press and Publicity Committee.
    - Articles, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 47)
    - Anniversary Video, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 48)
    - Black Entertainment Television, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 49)
    - Black Imaging in the Media, 1996-1997 (Box 42, Folder 50)
    - Branch Connections, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 51)
    - Brown, Byrd, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 52)
    - Clippings, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 53)
    - Committee, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 54)
    - Communications, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 55)
    - Communications Committee, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 56)
    - Convention, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - County NAACP Procedures, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Courier Column, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - The Crisis, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Election Misconduct, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Event Flyers, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Flyers, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - General, 2001-2004 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Hoover, J. Edgar, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - KDKA Radio, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Legacy of Affirmative Action, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Letter to the Editor, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Letters to the Editor, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Marketing Proposal, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Media Forum, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Media Relations, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Media Summit, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Media Summit, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - New Pittsburgh Courier, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - News, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - News Articles, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - News Conferences, 1997-2001 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - News Releases, 1995-2002 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Newsletters, 1974-2004 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Pittsburgh Courier, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Pittsburgh Radio Organization, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Press Releases, 1996-2004 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Promotion Meeting, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Radio Spot, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Redmond, Gina, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Request for News Coverage, undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Seate, Mike, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - SoJournal Truth, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Speeches, 2004-2006 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Tourism Industry, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - WAMO, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Women's Issues, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - WPXI, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Media Relations, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 48)
    - M. Gayle Moss in the News, 2006-2007 (Box 42, Folder 49)
    - National Organization in the News, March 2007 (Box 42, Folder 50)
    - News Releases, 2000-2004 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - Prison Affairs, 1995-2004; 17.
    This subseries contains materials relating to the NAACP's concerns regarding prisons and prisoners' rights in the region, from 1995 to 2004. Included in this are the partial records of the Prison Affairs Committee.
    - Bureau of Corrections Report, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - Complaints, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - Death Penalty, 2000-2002 (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - District Attorney, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 43)
    - Execution Appeals, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 44)
    - General, 1996-2004 (Box 42, Folder 45)
    - Jury Awareness, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - Jury Pool, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 47)
    - Prisoners' Rights, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 48)
    - SCIP, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 49)
    - The Program for Female Offenders, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 52)
    - "Prison, Politics, and Fear", 2006 (Box 42, Folder 53)
  - Projects and Events, 1995-2006; 18.
    This subseries contains materials relating to special events and projects the NAACP sponsored or spearheaded, from 1995 to 2006.
    - African American Cultural Facility, 1998-2000 (Box 42, Folder 50)
    - African American Cultural Facility, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 51)
    - African American Cultural Facility, 2000-2001 (Box 42, Folder 52)
    - African American Cultural Museum, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - African American Extravaganza, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - African American Heritage Project, 2004-2006 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Alma Speed Fox Building, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Black Extravaganza, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Black History, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Black History Month, undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Black Media Summit, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Black Radical Congress, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Black Unity Plan, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - BREAD, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Candlelight Vigil for Justice, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Civil Rights Discount Program, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Civil Rights Hall of Fame, undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Community Coordination, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Community Groups, undated (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Community Leadership Forum, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Community Support Project, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Conventions, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Count Every Vote Rally, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Coyne Salute, undated (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Day of Honor, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Diamonds in the Rough, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Doll Project, undated (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Enough is Enough, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Events Flyers, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Evers-Williams, Myrlie, visit, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Fifth-Forbes Project, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Freedom Corner, 1998-2002 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Freedom Fund Dinner, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Freedom Fund Banquet, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Freedom Jazz Concert, 2000-2002 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Freedom Jazz Concert, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Freedom Jazz Concert, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Freedom Sunday, 2003-2004 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Freedom Unlimited Mural, undated (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - Hall of Fame, undated (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - History Project, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Holiday Heritage, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - Holiday Heritage, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - Holiday Heritage, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 41)
    - Holiday Heritage, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 42)
    - Holiday Heritage, undated (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 44)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 45)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 1997-2001 (Box 23, Folder 46-48)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 49)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 50-51)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 52)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 53)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 2003-2004 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 3-4)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 2004-2005 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Human Rights Music Fest, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Indiana County Freedom Fund Banquet, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Installation, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Job Fair, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Journey for Justice, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - July 97, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Juneteenth, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Forum Series, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Million Man March, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Mon Valley Branch Human Rights Dinner, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Monte Carlo Night, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Mural Project, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - National Convention, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - National Convention, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 19-23)
    - National Convention, 1998-2000 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - National Convention, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - National Convention, 2000-2002 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - National Convention, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - National Convention, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 28-29)
    - Office Opening, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Plan B, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Plans for Progress, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Plans for Progress, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Redeem the Dream, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Regional Conference, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 35-36)
    - South African Doll Project, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Special Events Committee, 1998-2001 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - State Conference, 1995-1999 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - State Conference, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - State Conference, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - State Conference, 2001 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - State Conference, 2002-2005 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Summit Against Racism, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Summit of Black Imaging in the Media, 2004 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Tennis Tournament, 2001-2005 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Testimonial Banquet, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Thanksgiving Fundraiser, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Unity Fountain, 2002 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Enough is Enough Rally, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 54)
    - Freedom Jazz Concert, undated (Box 42, Folder 55)
    - Gospel Fest, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 56)
    - Medgar Evans Dinner, 2013 (Box 42, Folder 57)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 1996 (Box 42, Folder 58)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 59)
    - Human Rights Dinner, 2004-2006 (Box 42, Folder 60)
    - Human Rights Music Festival, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 61)
    - National Convention, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 62)
    - National Convention, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 63)
  - Race Relations, 1995-2004; 19.
    This subseries contains materials relating to tensions in race relations and the NAACP's attempts to mediate these disputes, from 1995 to 2004.
    - Census, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Days of Dialogue, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - General, 1995-2000 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - General, 2000-2003 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - General, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - General, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - General, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Landmark Forum, undated (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - National Race Symposium, 1997-1999 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - National Race Relations Symposium, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - White Privilege, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Brown v. The Board of Education, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 64)
    - Coretta Scott King, 2006 (Box 42, Folder 65)
    - "Lumumba: Death of a Prophet", 2002 (Box 42, Folder 66)
    - K Leroy Irvis, undated (Box 42, Folder 67)
    - Racial Disparities with Cocaine Sentencing, 2007 (Box 42, Folder 68)
    - Lunch Hour for Racial Sensitivity, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 69)
  - Religious Affairs, 1993-2005; 20.
    This subseries contains materials related to the NAACP's involvement in religious organizations in Pittsburgh, from 1993 to 2005. Included in this are the partial records of the Religious Affairs Committee.
    - Breakfast with the Commissioner, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Clergy and Churches United, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Community Violence, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Ebenezer Baptist Church, 2004 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Freedom Sunday, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - General, 1993-1997 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - General, 1999-2002 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - General, 2003-2004 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Gospel Fest, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Gospel Fest, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Gospel Fest, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Meetings, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Meetings, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Ministerial, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Ministerial Support, undated (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Pittsburgh Interfaith Impact Network, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - Religion and Race Council, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - Smith, Thomas, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 42-43)
    - Trinity A.M.E Church, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 44)
    - War, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 45)
    - Heritage Project, 2005 (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - Pittsburgh Interfaith Impact Network, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Youth, 1995-2004; 21.
    This subseries contains information related to the NAACP's involvement with youth in the community, from 1995 to 2004. Included in this are the partial records of the Youth Committee.
    - ACT-SO, 1996-1997 (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - ACT-SO, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 47)
    - ACT-SO, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 48)
    - ACT-SO, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 49)
    - ACT-SO, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 50)
    - ACT-SO Sponsorship, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 51)
    - Children and Youth Services, undated (Box 42, Folder 52)
    - College Chapter, undated (Box 42, Folder 53)
    - Committee to Recruit Young Adults, 2001 (Box 42, Folder 54)
    - Curfew, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - General, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Initiatives, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Kingian Non-Violence Youth Summit, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - March for Peace, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - National Family Heritage Coalition, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - POISE Foundation Youth Fund, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Resumes, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - State Conventions, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Trust Fund Committee, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Urban Youth Action, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - You and the Police, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Young Adult Leadership, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Young Adult Recruitment, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Youth Celebration of Success, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Youth Council, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Youth Council, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Youth Council, 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Youth Council Fund, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Youth Crime Prevention Council, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Youth Work Trust Fund, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Youth Council, 1995 (Box 42, Folder 48)
- Personal, 1945-2003; IV.
  This series contains materials related to Stevens' personal pursuits outside of the NAACP. The main bulk of this series contains information on his musical career, but there is also material concerning his education and family. This series contains news articles, flyers, playbills, correspondence, sheet music, awards, commencement brochures, and a school yearbook.
  - African American Leadership Directory, 1999-2001 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Alpha Omicron Lambda, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Articles, 1968-2003 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Awards and Honors, 1970-2003 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Birth Certificate, 1945 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - City Council Campaign, undated (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Clinton Inauguration, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence, 1983-2000 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence, 2004, undated (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Elementary School, 1955-1960 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Fall Jazz Classic, 1993 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Fall Jazz Classic, 1995-2003 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Holiday Inn, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Leadership, 2002 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Music Resume, undated (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Performances, 1990-2003 (Box 42, Folder 38-39)
  - Pittsburgh Jazz Society, 1997-2002 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Pittsburgh Magazine, 1997-2003 (Box 42, Folder 41)
  - Resume, undated (Box 42, Folder 42)
  - Reviews, 1990-1999 (Box 42, Folder 43)
  - Schenley Reunion, undated (Box 42, Folder 44)
  - Sinatra Tribute, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 45)
  - Songwriting, 1989-1997 (Box 42, Folder 46)
  - Speech Material, 1995-1997, undated (Box 42, Folder 47)
  - Stevens, Georgetta, 1960-1996 (Box 42, Folder 48)
  - Stevens, Jaspar, 1966-1997 (Box 42, Folder 49)
  - Trinity A.M.E Church, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 50)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1973-1977 (Box 42, Folder 51)
  - University of Pittsburgh The Owl Yearbook, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 52)
  - Al Sharpton (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Awards/Recognitions, 1964-2009 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Awards/Recognitions, 2010-2014 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Entertainment/Music, 2005-2009 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Events, 2002-2013 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Jazz in Pittsburgh, 2005-2008 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Kane, Kelli Stevens, 2012-2013 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Mayview, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Meetings (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Items (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Music, 1971-2005 (Box 40, Folder 33A)
  - Music Pictures, undated (Box 40, Folder 33B)
  - Old Resumes, undated (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Obituaries, 1996-2008 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Personal Correspondences, 2005-2008 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Personal Notes, Undated (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - No Grey Hair, 2005 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Pitt Magazine, 2007-2008 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Pitt Magazine, 2008-2009 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Speeches (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Strategic Diversity (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Talk Magazine, 2005-2013 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Trinity A.M.E. Church, 2008 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Pictures, undated (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Circle of Courage Award, 2012 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Photo Appearances (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper on August Wilson Center for African American Culture, 2014 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Circle of Courage Award, August 2014 (Box 44, Item 2)
  - Pennsylvania House of Representatives Citation, June 2010 (Box 44, Item 3)
  - August Wilson Center for African American Culture Appreciation Plaque, July 2010 (Box 44, Item 4)
  - 911 Tactical Airlift Cp. Appreciation Plaque, undated (Box 44, Item 5)
  - Park Place AME Church Community Service Award, February 2009 (Box 44, Item 6)
  - Service Appreciation Clock, June 1999 (Box 44, Item 7)